<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-02T12:12:09.664Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-02T12:12:09.664Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet: Kajabi President Sean Kim]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5705</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/info-diet-sean-kim/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet offers a peek into the personally curated feeds and media habits of the people shaping the future. In each installment, a different builder spends two days chronicling everything they read, follow, listen to, and watch in order to stay ahead of the curve. This time: Sean Kim, president and chief product officer at... Read More
The post Info Diet: Kajabi President Sean Kim appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Marketplace Retention Metric Most Ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5703</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/gmv-retention-marketplace-metric/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you’re running a marketplace startup — let’s call it ACo — that allows consumers to sell spare items they have around the house. You notice after a few months that only 25% of your new sellers are coming back each month, but they’re selling just as much as they did in that first month.... Read More
The post The Marketplace Retention Metric Most Ignore appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will It Scale? Applying Data, Science, and Economics to the Art of Ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5386</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/data-science-and-economics-art-of-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John List is chief economist at Walmart (a title he previously held at both Lyft and Uber) and a professor of economics at the University of Chicago. He recently published a book titled The Voltage Effect: How to Make Good Ideas Great and Great Ideas Scale. In this interview, List discusses some of the book’s... Read More
The post Will It Scale? Applying Data, Science, and Economics to the Art of Ideas appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John List and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Decentralized Biotech]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5669</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/a-guide-to-decentralized-biotech/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American biotech has traditionally been a centralized industry, with most companies clustered in a handful of cities and operating with teams of in-house scientists. When biotech first gained its footing in the 1980s, there were good reasons for its centralized structure, including geographic proximity to the universities supplying talent and intellectual property. But recent changes... Read More
The post A Guide to Decentralized Biotech appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelynn Pearl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Your Mental Health While Running a Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5369</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/managing-your-mental-health-while-running-a-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an excerpt from Zero to IPO: Over $1 Trillion of Actionable Advice from the World’s Most Successful Entrepreneurs by Frederic Kerrest, pp. 164-171, (McGraw Hill, April 2022). Kerrest co-founded Okta – an enterprise identity management company – in 2009 and currently serves as its executive vice chairperson and chief operating officer. I’ve heard a lot... Read More
The post Managing Your Mental Health While Running a Startup appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederic Kerrest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Marketplace 100: 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5354</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/marketplace-100/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 marks our third year releasing the Marketplace 100, a ranking of the largest consumer-facing marketplace startups and private companies.  When we started this series in early 2020 (based on data from 2019), we had no way of knowing how volatile the next few years would be. Many businesses were temporarily shuttered by covid, especially... Read More
The post The Marketplace 100: 2022 appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Moore and Brandon Barros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Drive Business Growth By Fostering Your Community]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5202</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/drive-business-growth-by-fostering-community-gtc/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s familiar with the concept of a go-to-market (GTM) plan, but in the world of bottom-up adoption and product-led growth, a go-to-community (GTC) plan is equally as important.  As the name suggests, go-to-community is the process of operationalizing and optimizing your community-building efforts to align them with business outcomes. Growing a healthy community can create... Read More
The post How to Drive Business Growth By Fostering Your Community appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Woods</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why China’s Version of Email Marketing Is So Effective]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5163</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/private-traffic-is-chinas-version-of-email-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to ecommerce, last year in China often means this year (or next) in the U.S. Numerous online shopping trends have swept China before landing stateside one or two years later. This is happening now with super apps (e.g., WeChat and Doordash), meaning platforms that customers initially use for one purpose (like ordering food... Read More
The post Why China’s Version of Email Marketing Is So Effective appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connie Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralization for Web3 Builders: Principles, Models, How]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5098</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/web3-decentralization-models-framework-principles-how-to/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T16:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The promise of decentralization has been heavily discussed and debated, from why it matters to the bigger question of who will control the software that powers the internet. These questions are critical, because as we have seen, when control is held in the hands of a very few, encroachments on personal freedom, choice, and privacy... Read More
The post Decentralization for Web3 Builders: Principles, Models, How appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Jennings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ‘Community Composability’ Help Web2 Users Make the Jump to Web3?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5068</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/can-community-composability-help-web2-users-make-the-jump-to-web3/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T17:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 has infiltrated mainstream culture, from Paris Hilton showcasing her NFTs on the Tonight Show to ConstitutionDAO attempting to buy one of the last remaining copies of the Constitution. Joining web3, however, is still a complex and confusing process geared toward early adopters. There’s a whole cohort of digitally native people — let’s call them... Read More
The post Can ‘Community Composability’ Help Web2 Users Make the Jump to Web3? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jenny Wang and Michael Chiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>