<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-12T19:14:32.493Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-10-12T19:14:32.493Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Applying Machine Learning to Biology is Hard – But Worth It]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7114</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/why-applying-machine-learning-to-biology-is-hard-but-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Lin is CSO of Freenome, which is developing blood-based tests for early cancer detection, starting with colon cancer. He is a pioneer in developing computational approaches to extract insights from large-scale genomic data, having spearheaded the computational analyses of the first genome-wide sequencing studies in multiple cancer types.  Lin talked to Future about the... Read More
The post Why Applying Machine Learning to Biology is Hard – But Worth It appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimmy Lin and Nicole Neuman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did We Overeat on Software?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7096</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/did-we-overeat-on-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a little over a decade since Marc Andreesen famously declared that software was eating the world. He was right. Now, we’re in a new phase: There is powerful software everywhere we look, and we’ve been consuming it without much regard for the long-term effects. So much so that, today, we’re faced with an... Read More
The post Did We Overeat on Software? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Safundzic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Cities Have an API Problem. Startups Can Fix It.]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7073</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/cities-broken-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Cities are technological artifacts,” Kevin Kelly once wrote, “the largest technology we make.” What if we looked at America’s cities not metaphorically as tech, but literally as a technological system? Rather than fighting about politics, we’d ask our cities the mundane questions that engineers and entrepreneurs ask about any other technology: “Is it expensive to... Read More
The post Our Cities Have an API Problem. Startups Can Fix It. appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Caceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>