<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-03-27T07:26:56.052Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-03-27T07:26:56.052Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data50: The World’s Top Data Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4859</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/data50/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a decade after the idea of “big data” was first born, data continues to be one of the most important and furiously growing innovation drivers across both large enterprises and new startups. From providing pulse checks that are foundational to business operations to intelligently automating daily tasks through machine learning, data has become the... Read More
The post Data50: The World’s Top Data Startups appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Li, Sarah Wang and Jamie Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Data Rights Stifle Innovation in the DoD (and How to Fix Them)]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4853</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/data-rights-stifle-innovation-in-the-dod/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an edited and abridged version of a post that originally ran on the Anduril blog. It would be difficult to find a more prophetic blog post in the history of technology commentary than Marc Andreessen’s 2011 “Why Software is Eating the World.” Over the past decade, software companies have driven the lion’s share... Read More
The post How Data Rights Stifle Innovation in the DoD (and How to Fix Them) appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak Siavoshy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Key to Enterprise Sales Is Understanding Enterprises]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4839</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-key-to-enterprise-sales/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-17T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unqork founder and CEO Gary Hoberman took an unusual path to entrepreneurship, spending decades writing code and managing massive budgets on Wall Street (his prior role was executive vice president and global CIO for MetLife) before starting his own company. By his estimation, it was the best thing he could have done to set him... Read More
The post The Key to Enterprise Sales Is Understanding Enterprises appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Hoberman and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet: Modern Fertility CEO Afton Vechery]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4805</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/what-modern-fertility-founder-afton-vechery-reads/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T18:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet offers a peek into the personally curated feeds and media habits of the people shaping the future. In each installment, a different builder spends two days chronicling everything they read, follow, listen to, and watch in order to stay ahead of what’s next. This time: Afton Vechery, co-founder and CEO of the reproductive... Read More
The post Info Diet: Modern Fertility CEO Afton Vechery appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afton Vechery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaFold, GPT-3 and How to Augment Intelligence with AI (Pt. 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4642</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/alphafold-gpt-3-and-how-to-augment-intelligence-with-ai-pt-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T16:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we saw in Part 1, it’s possible to get started on a number of important problems by building augmentation infrastructure around the strengths of an artificial intelligence model. Does the model generate text? Build around text. Can it accurately predict 3D structures? Build around 3D structures. But taking an artificial intelligence system completely at... Read More
The post AlphaFold, GPT-3 and How to Augment Intelligence with AI (Pt. 2) appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niko Grupen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaFold, GPT-3 and How to Augment Intelligence with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4641</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/alphafold-gpt-3-and-how-to-augment-intelligence-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T16:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first post in a two-part series. Read Part 2 here. Around the same time that Alan Turing was shaping his theories of machine intelligence in Manchester, another future giant of the computing world, Douglas Engelbart, was developing an alternative computing paradigm over 5,000 miles away in the Bay Area.  Engelbart believed that... Read More
The post AlphaFold, GPT-3 and How to Augment Intelligence with AI appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niko Grupen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Decade of Deep Learning: How the AI Startup Experience Has Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4611</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/a-decade-of-deep-learning-ai-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The artificial intelligence field has evolved dramatically since the deep learning revolution kicked off in 2012, and Richard Socher has been around for all of it. He earned his PhD from Stanford working on NLP (natural language processing) before co-founding an AI startup called MetaMind in 2013. He then spent several years leading the AI... Read More
The post A Decade of Deep Learning: How the AI Startup Experience Has Evolved appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Socher and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>