<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-06T07:30:54.794Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-09-06T07:30:54.794Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research Twice, Build Once: How to Know Your Users as You Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7011</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/user-research-as-you-grow/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Far too many products still fail because there’s simply no demand for them. How does that happen? Or, how do so many startups launch entire businesses without realizing users didn’t need their products?  By overlooking user research.  Every tech company has to build and ship new products to continue growing. And, whether there are 10... Read More
The post Research Twice, Build Once: How to Know Your Users as You Grow appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Glasgow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grow or Die: A Framework for Turning Your Company Around Fast]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7009</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/grow-or-die-supergoals/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T18:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post originally ran here. Most great teams would agree, there’s nothing more powerful for executing on big ambitions than a clearly defined and well-communicated goal. But sometimes the stakes are much higher than usual. In these instances, a goal requires even more focus, execution, and clarity. All of these can be achieved through a... Read More
The post Grow or Die: A Framework for Turning Your Company Around Fast appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mignano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Synthetic Embryos Can and Can’t Do, Now and in the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6979</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/what-synthetic-embryos-can-do/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T14:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magdalena Zernicka-Goetz is the Bren Professor of Biology and Biological Engineering at the California Institute of Technology and a Professor of Stem Cell Biology and Development at the University of Cambridge. In this interview, we discuss recent advances in technologies that allow us to use stem cells to create embryo-like structures with a brain and... Read More
The post What Synthetic Embryos Can and Can’t Do, Now and in the Future appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Magda Zernicka-Goetz and Nicole Neuman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Fried on Why He Doesn’t Do Planning or Politics at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6947</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/jason-fried-basecamp-hey-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T15:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compared with many startups, 37signals cofounder Jason Fried’s views around workplace culture, structure, and strategy could be considered subversive. He’d call them “honest,” a word he uses often when describing his leadership style. The outspoken maker of Basecamp and HEY has cultivated a reputation as a tech industry contrarian over the past two decades with... Read More
The post Jason Fried on Why He Doesn’t Do Planning or Politics at Work appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fried and Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Through CC0 and IP for NFT Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6924</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/thinking-through-cc0-and-ip-for-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Web3 Water Cooler, a moderated Slack chat about a trending topic in crypto. This week’s participants are Orca Protocol’s Chase Chapman, Austin Hurwitz of Venice Music, and IP lawyer Nuzayra Haque-Shah. NFTs are a web3 innovation, but the intellectual property frameworks surrounding them have been borrowed from a web2 world. This leaves web3... Read More
The post Thinking Through CC0 and IP for NFT Communities appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chase Chapman, Nuzayra Haque-Shah, Austin Hurwitz and Jeff Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Insider’s Guide to Data Rooms: What to Know Before You Raise]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6886</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/insiders-guide-to-data-rooms-fundraising/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for your startup to fundraise. You prepare a deck, practice your pitch, and start reaching out to investors. If a first meeting goes well, it often ends with a request to share your “data room.” But what is a data room, and what should be included in it? What is a data room?... Read More
The post The Insider’s Guide to Data Rooms: What to Know Before You Raise appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justine Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Startups Will Win the War for Top Talent]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6869</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/remote-startups-hire-top-talent/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ease and speed with which you can now buy nearly anything — truly, anything — online is often taken for granted: not just food, but cars, homes, blue-chip art, even a college education. In the past 30 years, we have grown to trust the internet in a way we could never have imagined in... Read More
The post Remote Startups Will Win the War for Top Talent appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Herd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a GPT-3 for Science]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6859</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/how-to-build-gpt-3-for-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to create an image of velociraptors working on a skyscraper, in the style of “Lunch Atop A Skyscraper” of 1932? Use DALL-E. Want to create an imaginary standup comedy show by Peter Thiel, Elon Musk, and Larry Page? Use GPT-3. Want to deeply understand COVID-19 research and answer your questions based on evidence? Learn... Read More
The post How to Build a GPT-3 for Science appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Nicholson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Fear-Mongering Isn’t New—But It’s Time to Break the Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6827</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/cycle-of-tech-panics-build-for-tomorrow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Orben wanted to answer a very modern question: How do digital connections compare with other forms of connection?  It’s the kind of thing only a wonky, hyperanalytic person would think to ask. Orben is that person. She received a master’s in natural science from the University of Cambridge, and then went to the University... Read More
The post Tech Fear-Mongering Isn’t New—But It’s Time to Break the Cycle appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Feifer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unbundling Digital Identity Unlocks New Ways to Play and Build]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6809</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/unbundling-digital-identity-unlocks-new-ways-to-play-and-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who are you when you’re online? This question is all the more important as we spend more and more of our lives there. In the past decade, online usage has more than doubled; for GenZ, it’s even greater. How we spend that time has also changed as the early, transactional web has expanded to a... Read More
The post Unbundling Digital Identity Unlocks New Ways to Play and Build appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Radoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>