<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-12T22:06:07.602Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-07-12T22:06:07.602Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sales Enablement: The Underrated Cog of Enterprise Commercial Engines]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6354</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/sales-enablement-the-underrated-cog-of-enterprise-commercial-engines/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales enablement —the strategic use of people, processes, and technology to improve sales productivity and increase revenue — is the (usually) missing key for sales organizations that want to evolve beyond a handful of overachievers and into a well-oiled, agile, and high-performing commercial machine. Along with go-to-market — how an organization engages with customers to... Read More
The post Sales Enablement: The Underrated Cog of Enterprise Commercial Engines appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vassilis Tziokas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantifying Disease Risk Using Genomics: the New Paradigm]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6410</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/polygenic-risk-score-disease-genomics/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Donnelly is a professor of statistical science at the University of Oxford and the CEO of Genomics PLC, which uses large-scale human genetic data to inform healthcare and drug discovery. In this interview he, Lauren Richardson, and a16z general partner Vineeta Agarwala discuss the concept of polygenic risk scores with and how this lets... Read More
The post Quantifying Disease Risk Using Genomics: the New Paradigm appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Donnelly, Vineeta Agarwala and Lauren Richardson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware, Cyber-Savviness, and the Public-Private Security Connection]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6435</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/cisa-deputy-director-cybersecurity-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nitin Natarajan is the deputy director of CISA (Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency), and has extensive experience in the cybersecurity space, including overseeing critical infrastructure for the U.S. National Security Council and the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services.  In this discussion with a16z general partner Joel de la Garza (who was previously chief... Read More
The post Ransomware, Cyber-Savviness, and the Public-Private Security Connection appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Natarajan and Joel de la Garza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mid-year Recap: Web3 and Science Collide]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6415</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/first-half-2022-web3-decentralized-science-desci/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists have acknowledged for years that there are large structural problems in science: the funding system is dysfunctional, results are frequently unreproducible, and scientific knowledge is siloed. Recently, a small but passionate group of technologists, scientists, and entrepreneurs have envisioned web3 and blockchain-based tools as potentially breaking these structural logjams. This has become the decentralized... Read More
The post Mid-year Recap: Web3 and Science Collide appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Future Editorial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto/Web3 So Far in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6471</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/crypto-web3-so-far-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-29T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By the time you think you’ve got crypto figured out, something new emerges — or an old innovation comes back to the fore. Since the last Crypto Winter thawed, we’ve experienced a DeFi Summer, scaled the ramparts of an NFT revolution, and then logged onto Discord for a DAO resurgence. As enthusiasm over prices gives... Read More
The post Crypto/Web3 So Far in 2022 appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Future Editorial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recognizing the Next CRISPR-Level Tech for Biology]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6396</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/doudna-next-crispr-technology-to-engineer-biology/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-28T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jennifer Doudna won the 2020 Nobel Prize in Chemistry for her co-discovery of CRISPR/Cas9, a versatile genome editing platform. In the decade since its discovery the toolbox of CRISPR technologies has exploded, acting like rocket fuel for curiosity-driven science. It is also increasingly a foundational technology for many biotech companies. In this conversation, Doudna chats... Read More
The post Recognizing the Next CRISPR-Level Tech for Biology appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Doudna and Vijay Pande</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year in AI So Far: Massive Models and How to Use Them]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6459</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/the-year-in-ai-so-far-massive-models-and-how-to-use-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-27T14:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of artificial intelligence and machine learning moves very fast. So fast, in fact, that it’s remarkable to think that it was only a decade ago when the AlexNet model dominated the ImageNet competition and kicked off the process that made deep learning a bona fide technology movement. Today, after years of headlines about... Read More
The post The Year in AI So Far: Massive Models and How to Use Them appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Future Editorial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget “Open-Source” Algorithms — Focus on Experiments Instead]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6349</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/forget-open-source-algorithms-focus-on-experiments-instead/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-24T16:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, I led a small team at Instagram that designed and built one of the largest content distribution experiments in history: the introduction of a personalized ranking algorithm to the platform’s (then) 500 million users. Anticipating controversy, we spent the next several years scientifically measuring differences between people receiving this evolving “recommendation algorithm” (as... Read More
The post Forget “Open-Source” Algorithms — Focus on Experiments Instead appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Dimson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the Metaverse: New Opportunities in Games Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6371</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/metaverse-infrastructure-technology-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-23T16:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You install that new Parkour game that everyone’s talking about, and instantly your avatar gains a new set of skills. After a few minutes in the tutorial level, running up walls and vaulting over obstacles, you’re ready for a bigger challenge. You teleport yourself into one of your favorite games, Grand Theft Auto: Metaverse, following... Read More
The post Unlocking the Metaverse: New Opportunities in Games Infrastructure appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Gwertzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Two Things We’ll Need for the Next AlphaFold]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6342</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/koller-insitro-drug-discovery-ai-alphafold/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T20:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daphne Koller is the founder and CEO of insitro. Prior to insitro, she served as Chief Computing Officer at Calico. She was also a Professor in the Computer Science department at Stanford University before making a mid-career transition to co-found Coursera.   In this interview, she shares some of the challenges with creating accurate machine learning... Read More
The post The Two Things We’ll Need for the Next AlphaFold appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daphne Koller and Nicole Neuman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>