<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-11T11:04:15.468Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-05-11T11:04:15.468Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB CTO On Working with Cloud Providers and Working in Southeast Asia]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5845</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/mongodb-cto-cloud-providers-southeast-asia/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T14:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB CTO Mark Porter has been on all sides of the technology industry. He was most recently CTO of core technology and transport at Grab, a super-app serving Southeast Asia, and prior to that held leadership roles at Amazon Web Services and Oracle, among other places. In this interview, he shares his views on the... Read More
The post MongoDB CTO On Working with Cloud Providers and Working in Southeast Asia appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Porter and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Essential Ingredients of a Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5821</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/7-essential-ingredients-of-a-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T17:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a lot of buzz about “the metaverse” since its coinage in the ‘90s, but especially during the pandemic (given the surge in online activity), and even more so after Facebook changed its name to Meta.  Is this just a bit of opaque marketing-speak? What is a metaverse exactly? How does one define... Read More
The post 7 Essential Ingredients of a Metaverse appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Harkavy, Eddy Lazzarin and Arianna Simpson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockets, Jets, and Chips: How to Modernize U.S. Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5802</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/why-the-time-is-right-to-disrupt-defense-and-aerospace/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are edited highlights from a recent Clubhouse discussion among Hadrian founder and CEO Chris Power, a16z partners Katherine Boyle and Marc Andreessen, and Not Boring newsletter author Packy McCormick. The dialogue here is part of a broader discussion that touches on a number of issues related to launching a modern manufacturing business, including software... Read More
The post Rockets, Jets, and Chips: How to Modernize U.S. Manufacturing appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Power, Katherine Boyle, Marc Andreessen and Packy McCormick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Start Building a Community, Master These Two Concepts]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5771</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/to-start-building-a-community-master-these-two-concepts/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T16:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Increasingly, building a successful startup involves not only building a product that people can’t get enough of, but also building an engaged, loyal community around that product. Today, most founders are acutely aware of the value of community. In CMX’s 2021 Community Industry Report, 86% of respondents (community managers from 508 different companies) said community... Read More
The post To Start Building a Community, Master These Two Concepts appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amber Atherton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Search Is Boutique]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5729</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-future-of-search-is-boutique/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an edited version of a post that originally ran here. For most queries, Google search is pretty underwhelming these days. Google is great at answering questions with an objective answer, like “# of billionaires in the world” or “What is the population of Iceland?” It’s pretty bad at answering questions that require judgment... Read More
The post The Future of Search Is Boutique appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sari Azout</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet: Kajabi President Sean Kim]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5705</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/info-diet-sean-kim/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet offers a peek into the personally curated feeds and media habits of the people shaping the future. In each installment, a different builder spends two days chronicling everything they read, follow, listen to, and watch in order to stay ahead of the curve. This time: Sean Kim, president and chief product officer at... Read More
The post Info Diet: Kajabi President Sean Kim appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Marketplace Retention Metric Most Ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5703</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/gmv-retention-marketplace-metric/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T15:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you’re running a marketplace startup — let’s call it ACo — that allows consumers to sell spare items they have around the house. You notice after a few months that only 25% of your new sellers are coming back each month, but they’re selling just as much as they did in that first month.... Read More
The post The Marketplace Retention Metric Most Ignore appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will It Scale? Applying Data, Science, and Economics to the Art of Ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5386</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/data-science-and-economics-art-of-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T14:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John List is chief economist at Walmart (a title he previously held at both Lyft and Uber) and a professor of economics at the University of Chicago. He recently published a book titled The Voltage Effect: How to Make Good Ideas Great and Great Ideas Scale. In this interview, List discusses some of the book’s... Read More
The post Will It Scale? Applying Data, Science, and Economics to the Art of Ideas appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John List and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Decentralized Biotech]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5669</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/a-guide-to-decentralized-biotech/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T00:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American biotech has traditionally been a centralized industry, with most companies clustered in a handful of cities and operating with teams of in-house scientists. When biotech first gained its footing in the 1980s, there were good reasons for its centralized structure, including geographic proximity to the universities supplying talent and intellectual property. But recent changes... Read More
The post A Guide to Decentralized Biotech appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelynn Pearl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Your Mental Health While Running a Startup]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5369</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/managing-your-mental-health-while-running-a-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-18T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an excerpt from Zero to IPO: Over $1 Trillion of Actionable Advice from the World’s Most Successful Entrepreneurs by Frederic Kerrest, pp. 164-171, (McGraw Hill, April 2022). Kerrest co-founded Okta – an enterprise identity management company – in 2009 and currently serves as its executive vice chairperson and chief operating officer. I’ve heard a lot... Read More
The post Managing Your Mental Health While Running a Startup appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederic Kerrest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>