<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-06-20T19:04:03.890Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-06-20T19:04:03.890Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide to NFT Memberships for Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6289</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/a-practical-guide-to-nft-memberships-for-creators/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-16T14:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2021, Chris Dixon wrote about how creators can use NFTs to monetize their “1,000 true fans.” Since then, NFT use-cases have multiplied. Case in point: The rise of NFT memberships, which require fans to hold a specific NFT to join a private community and enjoy its perks. NFT memberships give creators a way to... Read More
The post A Practical Guide to NFT Memberships for Creators appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Yang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete Guide to Acquihires]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6282</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/all-about-acquihires/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s ever-competitive environment to drive growth, identifying and hiring key talent through a structured transaction — known as an “acquihire” — has become an increasingly popular and effective way for companies to address hiring needs and accelerate product innovation and development.  Often joining the acquiring company as a unit or existing team, employers also... Read More
The post The Complete Guide to Acquihires appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Blackwood and Tina Ferguson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Synthetic Biology and Pond Scum Deliver Carbon-Neutral Manufacturing?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6270</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/synbio-algae-carbon-neutral-biomanufacturing/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T18:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetic biology has long promised to make production of medicines, foods, chemicals and materials cheaper and more sustainable. Yet, while many products can now be made through synbio, the bio-based manufacturing revolution is still not here. A major bottleneck to realizing the opportunity of synbio is the production process: the existing options are tricky and... Read More
The post Can Synthetic Biology and Pond Scum Deliver Carbon-Neutral Manufacturing? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nusqe Spanton and Nicole Neuman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Software Supply Chain Needs More Security]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6252</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/securing-the-software-supply-chain/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-09T16:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kim Lewandowski is co-founder and head of product at security startup Chainguard. Prior to Chainguard, she worked as a product manager at Google, most recently with a focus on securing the company’s development pipeline and the open source tools it used.  In this interview, she discusses the concept of a secure software supply chain and... Read More
The post Why the Software Supply Chain Needs More Security appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Lewandowski and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet: Peanut CEO Michelle Kennedy]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6216</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/info-diet-peanut-ceo-michelle-kennedy/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet offers a peek into the personally curated feeds and media habits of the people shaping the future. In each installment, a different builder spends two days chronicling all the content they consume in order to stay ahead of the curve. This time: Michelle Kennedy, founder and CEO of Peanut, an online community to... Read More
The post Info Diet: Peanut CEO Michelle Kennedy appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Iron Man Model: How Startups and the Military Can Work Together]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6201</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/the-iron-man-model-startups-military/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-03T14:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Afghanistan. North Korea. Russia. The South China Sea. Open a newspaper these days and you’ll read about the numerous problems facing America’s military. Global threats and a dwindling technological advantage have caused the Pentagon to cozy up to Silicon Valley, a relationship from which Palantir and Anduril are but two successful outcomes. Yet, most dual-use... Read More
The post The Iron Man Model: How Startups and the Military Can Work Together appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Decker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Techniques for Building Reliable AI Models]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6009</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/7-techniques-for-building-reliable-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-27T14:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an edited excerpt from Trustworthy AI: A Business Guide for Navigating Trust and Ethics in AI by Beena Ammanath (Wiley, March 2022). Ammanath is executive director of the Global Deloitte AI Institute and leads Trustworthy & Ethical Technology at Deloitte. She has held leadership positions in artificial intelligence and data science at multiple... Read More
The post 7 Techniques for Building Reliable AI Models appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beena Ammanath</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Trust and Assessing Integrity as You Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6029</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/building-trust-and-assessing-integrity-as-you-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T14:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Establishing trustworthiness early is a fundamental part of the interview process. Nothing else matters if you don’t think you can trust someone. Hopefully, you’ll build trust by way of multiple interviews, references, working sessions, etc. — but how can you get comfortable with someone you are meeting for the first time in the interview process,... Read More
The post Building Trust and Assessing Integrity as You Interview appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Stump</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>