<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-30T22:05:25.963Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-07-30T22:05:25.964Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s After Proof of Stake for Ethereum?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6596</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/how-the-merge-will-impact-future-ethereum-upgrades/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T15:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s biggest-ever upgrade — the move to a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism — is right around the corner. But while the Merge should add security and sustainability, it doesn’t include sharding, the long-anticipated method of scaling the network.  In Part I of our conversation with Ethereum Foundation (EF) researcher Danny Ryan, who’s helped coordinate the upgrade... Read More
The post What’s After Proof of Stake for Ethereum? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Ryan and Jeff Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Merge Means for Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6585</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/what-the-merge-means-for-ethereum-with-danny-ryan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T15:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of research, development and testing, Ethereum will transition from proof of work to proof of stake in the coming months. Instead of “miners” using computational energy to process transactions, “validators” will lock up, or stake, their assets in the network in return for ETH rewards. The upshot is increased security and a much... Read More
The post What the Merge Means for Ethereum appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Ryan and Jeff Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cilium, Service Meshes, and the Future of Enterprise Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6564</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/kubernetes-networking-and-finding-the-vmware-of-cloud-native/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Graf is the co-founder and CTO of Isovalent, and creator of a popular open source (and cloud native) networking technology called Cilium. Cilium is built atop a kernel-level Linux technology called eBPF. In this interview, Graf discusses the roles that Cilium and eBPF play in the growing cloud-native networking ecosystem, as well some broader... Read More
The post Cilium, Service Meshes, and the Future of Enterprise Networking appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Graf and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Domain Experts in Deep Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6537</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/the-rise-of-domain-experts-in-deep-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Howard is an artificial intelligence researcher and the co-founder of fast.ai, a platform for non-experts to learn artificial intelligence and machine learning. Prior to starting fast.ai, he founded multiple companies — including FastMail and Enlitic, a pioneer in applying deep learning to the medical field — and was president and chief scientist of machine-learning... Read More
The post The Rise of Domain Experts in Deep Learning appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Howard and Derrick Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Expand Your Marketplace Business, According to 14 Operators]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6498</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/when-where-how-to-expand-marketplace-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the world’s leading consumer marketplaces looked like completely different businesses at their inception. Amazon was famously an online bookseller, while Uber started as a black car service. DoorDash launched as “Palo Alto Delivery” (reflecting its narrow geographic range), while Booking.com exclusively helped travelers find hotels in the Netherlands.  This type of focused launch... Read More
The post When to Expand Your Marketplace Business, According to 14 Operators appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justine Moore and John Koelliker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet: a16z Crypto’s Elena Burger]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6502</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/info-diet-a16z-crypto-elena-burger/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Info Diet offers a peek into the personally curated feeds and media habits of the people shaping the future. In each installment, a different builder spends two days chronicling all the content they consume in order to stay ahead of the curve. This time: Elena Burger, a deal partner on the a16z crypto team, where... Read More
The post Info Diet: a16z Crypto’s Elena Burger appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elena Burger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Glittering Treasure in Your Genome’s Junk]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6488</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/the-glittering-treasure-in-your-genomes-junk/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rick Young is a professor of biology at MIT who studies RNA that is transcribed from the part of the genome that does not code for proteins, known as non-coding DNA. This part of the genome was once referred to as ‘junk DNA,’ which gives you a sense of what many thought of its value.... Read More
The post The Glittering Treasure in Your Genome’s Junk appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Young, Jorge Conde and Hanne Winarsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sales Enablement: The Underrated Cog of Enterprise Commercial Engines]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6354</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/sales-enablement-the-underrated-cog-of-enterprise-commercial-engines/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales enablement —the strategic use of people, processes, and technology to improve sales productivity and increase revenue — is the (usually) missing key for sales organizations that want to evolve beyond a handful of overachievers and into a well-oiled, agile, and high-performing commercial machine. Along with go-to-market — how an organization engages with customers to... Read More
The post Sales Enablement: The Underrated Cog of Enterprise Commercial Engines appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vassilis Tziokas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantifying Disease Risk Using Genomics: the New Paradigm]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6410</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/polygenic-risk-score-disease-genomics/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T15:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Donnelly is a professor of statistical science at the University of Oxford and the CEO of Genomics PLC, which uses large-scale human genetic data to inform healthcare and drug discovery. In this interview he, Lauren Richardson, and a16z general partner Vineeta Agarwala discuss the concept of polygenic risk scores with and how this lets... Read More
The post Quantifying Disease Risk Using Genomics: the New Paradigm appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Donnelly, Vineeta Agarwala and Lauren Richardson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware, Cyber-Savviness, and the Public-Private Security Connection]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6435</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/cisa-deputy-director-cybersecurity-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nitin Natarajan is the deputy director of CISA (Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency), and has extensive experience in the cybersecurity space, including overseeing critical infrastructure for the U.S. National Security Council and the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services.  In this discussion with a16z general partner Joel de la Garza (who was previously chief... Read More
The post Ransomware, Cyber-Savviness, and the Public-Private Security Connection appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Natarajan and Joel de la Garza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>